{
    "subject": "resource/Once_Upon_a_Time_(TV_series)",
    "predicate": "property/country",
    "object": "United States",
    "human_readable": "The country of origin for 'Once Upon a Time (TV series)' is United States.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.8370398879051208,
            "question": "What country produced the TV series 'Once Upon a Time'?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8274564743041992,
            "question": "What is the origin of the TV series 'Once Upon a Time'?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8080954551696777,
            "question": "Is 'Once Upon a Time' an American television show?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7546607255935669,
            "question": "Which country's television network aired 'Once Upon a Time'?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6324505805969238,
            "question": "In which country was 'Once Upon a Time' filmed?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6246033310890198,
            "question": "What nationality are the creators of 'Once Upon a Time'?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5339186787605286,
            "question": "Is 'Once Upon a Time' a US production?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5173501372337341,
            "question": "Where is 'Once Upon a Time' from?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5043403506278992,
            "question": "Could 'Once Upon a Time' be considered an American story?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4405002295970917,
            "question": "Is 'Once Upon a Time' known for its American storytelling style?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=The country of origin for 'Once Upon a Time (TV series)' is United States.",
            "html": "dbpedia_1897_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Could 'Once Upon a Time' be considered an American story?",
            "html": "dbpedia_1897_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Where is 'Once Upon a Time' from?",
            "html": "dbpedia_1897_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Is 'Once Upon a Time' a US production?",
            "html": "dbpedia_1897_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1897_10.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1897_11.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1897_12.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1897_13.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1897_16.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1897_18.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1897_4.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1897_6.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1897_7.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1897_8.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n\n\n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe documents confirm that \"Once Upon a Time\" is an American television series, indicating its country of origin as the United States."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "The Least Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}